







(</>) V

WORK EXPERIENCE

O Back-End Web Developer / Aug 2017 - Present As One Interactive Limited Quarry Bay, Hong Kong

Front-End Web Developer / Aug 2016 - Aug 2017 Flexibill Limited - Hong Kong Science Park Shatin, New Teritories, Hong Kong

Freelance Web Developer / Jan 2016 - Jul 2016 Ideanet Private Limited Central, Hong Kong

Graphic Artist & Photographer / Jul 2014 - Dec 2015 Alhan Events and Photography Doha, Qatar

Software Developer / Aug 2012 - Mar 2014 Gnosis Private Limited Inc. Hong Lim, Singapore

Freelance Web Developer / Jan 2013 - Aug 2013
Upwork.com previously Odesk.com
Vumiro Group - www.fjordflyfish.com
Sampateek - www.sampateek.com

Web Developer / May 2010 - Jul 2012
 Fishbase Information and Research Group Inc.
 IRRI, Laguna, Philippines

PROFESIONAL SKILLS

PHP & MYSQL

HTML & CSS

JAVASCRIPT

JQUERY

REACTJS

RUBY ON RAILS

PHOTOSHOP

PHOTOGRAPHY



ABOUT ME

Carly is a 28 year old Web Developer from the Philippines and currently located in Hong Kong. I am creative, friendly, team player, fast learner, dedicated, hardworking and loves learning about new technology, passionate on every task, and loves to travel and capturing moments.



EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION & TECHNOLOGY City College of Calamba 2010 Graduate

IELTS OVERALL BAND SCORE: 7.0 Speaking: 8.0 / Listening: 8.0 / Reading: 6.0 / Writing: 6.0 British Council IELTS, Thailand May 25, 2017

SHORT COURSES & TRAININGS

- O ReactJS Fundamentals Udemy Aug 2016
- O Ruby on Rails Beginners Guide Udemy Aug 2016
- O AWSDay Manila Amazon Web Services Training Feb 2014
- O Joomla Content Management System Training Jun 2012

- O Technical Workshop for D4Science Project Kiel, Germany (Jan 2011 & Oct 2011) and Orientation Meeting in Pisa, Italy (Jan 2011)
- O Course Instruction in Java Programming Level 1 & 2 Informatics Institute Sep - Oct 2010
- O Basic Electronics, PC Repair & Troubleshooting and Introduction to Digital Processing City College of Calamba Nov 2008